https://www.sfcable.com/privacy-policy.html

Menu Browse ProductsAdapters & Connectors (323)1/4" Plug/Jack1/4"/3.5mm/2.5mm/RCA Adapters3.5mm Plug/JackBNC ConnectorsBanana PlugsD-Sub ConnectorsD-Sub Gender ChangersD-Sub HoodsD-Sub Pin HeadersDVI/Displayport AdaptersDisplayPort and Mini DP AdaptersF Type ConnectorsF/RCA/BNC AdaptersFireWire Gender ChangersIDS SocketsMicrophone XLR Adapter and ConnectorsMini Tester AdapterModular Adapters (DB9, DB25 to RJ11/12, RJ45)Monitor & Printer Adapters (Sun & PC)Neutrik Professional Connectors Null Modem Adapters (DB9, DB25)Power PlugRCA Connectors/AdaptersS-Video AdaptersSerial Adapters (DB9, DB25)Speak-On ConnectorToslink AdaptersUSB Couplers / AdaptersUSB Keystone JacksUSB/PS2 Adapters (Keyboard/Mouse)Audio Video (564)1/4" to 1/4" Cables1/4" to RCA Cables2.5mm/3.5mm CablesAntennasAudio Stereo Y Adapter CableComponent Video CablesDigital Audio / Video CablesEthernet ExtendersMicrophonePattern GeneratorRCA / 3.5mm CablesRCA CablesRG59 Coaxial CablesRG6 Coax CablesRecessed Wall PlatesS-Video CablesSpeaker WiresSwitches & Splitters TV Signal SplitterWall PlatesWireless Presentation SystemsXLR
to 1/4" Stereo CableXLR / XLR CablesXLR to 1/4" CablesXLR to 3.5mm CablesXLR to RCA Cables
Bulk Wire & Cables (404)Cat 3 Bulk WireCat 5E Bulk WireCat 6/6A Bulk WireComposite Wire / Combo WireFire Alarm CableIrrigation CablesLandscape WirePC CablesPower Control CablesRG11 / RJ11 / RJ12 / RJ45RG58 / RG59 / RG6 Coaxial Bulk CableRG59/6 + Power WireSecurity Camera Power WireSecurity Sensor WireSpeaker Bulk Wire THHN Building WireThermostat Cables
Cables (620)BNC Breakout CablesBi-Directional Printer Cables (DB25, CN36)Cables for Apple/MACDB13W3 Sun CablesDB25 Serial CablesDB37 Serial CablesDB9 Serial CablesDB9/DB25 Modem CablesDVI Cables / AdaptersDisplayPort CablesFirewire (IEEE1394)IDE CablesIEEE-488 C24MF CablesKVM CablesKeyboard & Mouse Cables (PS/2 /Din5)Null Modem Cables (DB9, DB25)Power Supply Cables / AdaptersSATA / eSATA CablesSCSI Cables/AdaptersSVGA Monitor CablesSVGA Monitor Extension CablesSVGA/3.5mm Audio CablesEthernet Networking Cables (1977)Cat 5E CablesCat 6 CablesCat 6A CablesCat 7 Shielded Booted CablesCat 8 Shielded Booted CablesFiber Optic Patch Cables/Jumpers (325)50/125 10G Multimode Duplex50/125 Multimode Duplex62.5/125 Multimode Duplex9/125 Singlemode DuplexAdapters & ConnectorsAtenuatorMTP MultimodeHDMI (205)AccessoriesHDMI / IR ExtendersHDMI AdaptersHDMI CablesHDMI Cables TestersHDMI ConvertersHDMI DVI Cables / AdaptersHDMI Extension CablesHDMI MatrixHDMI SplittersHDMI SwitchesKeystone Jack/WallplateMicro HDMI (Type D) CablesMini HDMI (Type C) CablesPanel Mount HDMI CablesHome/Office Accessories (159)Desktop USB FanFlat TV Mounts1.5" NPT Ceiling MountCeiling MountDVD Wall MountDual Monitor Table StandFloor TV StandMid to Large (23~100") Wall MountProjector MountSmall to Mid (10~42") TV Wall MountSpeaker StandTV Mount AccesoriesGame AccessoriesNintendoSony PlaystationHousehold GadgetLighting/BulbsGarden LightsHalf Spiral BulbsHalogen BulbsIncandescent BulbsLED Light BulbsLED Panel LightsNight LightsOutdoor LED Lighting Reading LED LightsWork LightsPrinter TonerBrotherCanonDellHP/CompaqSamsungLaptop Accessories (149)ASUS AC AdapterAcer AC AdapterApple AC AdapterDell AC AdapterDelta AC AdaptersFujitsu AC AdapterGateway AC AdapterHP/Compaq AC AdapterIBM AC AdapterLCD Monitor AC AdapterLevono AC AdapterLiteon AC AdapterPanasonic AC AdapterPhilips AC AdapterSamsung AC AdapterSony AC AdapterToshiba AC AdapterUniversal AC AdapterMobile Device Accessories (112)Bluetooth SpeakerCar Mobile MountMobile AccessoriesSamsung GalaxyUSB Dock Sync & Mobile ChargersiPod/ iPad / iPhone Case CoveriPod/ iPad / iPhone-CableiTouch 4Networking (570)10/100 Switch1G Unmanaged Switch1G Unmanaged Uplink Switch1G Web Smart Switch1G Web Smart Uplink Switch3G Router66 Punch Down BlocksADSL FiltersADSL2+ ModemAccess PointBlank Patch PanelsCable ManagementCat 5E/6 CouplersCat 5E/6 RJ45 Surface mount JacksCisco Router CablesEtherWAN Media ConverterGigabit Smart SwitchKeystone Jacks (Cat3,Cat5E, Cat6, 6A)Keystone Module InsertsL2 1G Management SwitchL2 Full Management SwitchLED Patch PanelsMedia ConverterMounting HingesNetwork CardsNetwork Print ServerNetwork T SplittersNetworking RacksAccessoriesFloorstand RacksScrews & NutsShelvesWallmount RacksWorkstationsNorco TechPatch PanelsPoEPowerline EthernetRG58 BNC Coaxial CablesRJ45 BootsRJ45 Plugs for Cat 5e, Cat 6, Cat 6ARouterSpace Blank PanelWall PlatesWiFi Range ExtenderWireless AntennaWireless RouterWireless USB AdaptersPC Accessories (286)CPU Cooling FansCables TiesCables Tie GunCables Tie MountGrip-Clip Mounting ClipsHook and Loop Cables SockHook and Loop TiesMarker TiesNail-in TiesPlain TiesR-Type Cables ClampReleasable Cable TiesSpiral Zip WrapWall Mountable TiesCase Cooling FansHDD AdaptersHDD EnclosureI/O PeripheralsKVM SwitchesKeyboards/MiceLCD Screen PanelManual KVM SwitchesPower SuppliesSpeaker/EarphoneCeiling SpeakersEarcup HeadphoneEarphonesIn-Wall SpeakersMini SpeakersPatio Rock SpeakerWall Mount SpeakersTower CasesVGA SplittersVGA/PS2/Audio ExtendersPower Cords (564)American - US Power CordsC14 to NEMA 5-15R Power CordsComputer Power Extension CordCords - ApplianceExtension Power CordsHospital Grade Power CordIEC C13 Power CordsIEC C15 Power CordsIEC C19 Power CordsIEC C21 Power CordsIEC C5 Power CordsIEC C7 Power CordsIEC320 Power CordsC14 to C13 Power CordsC14 to C15 Power CordsC14 to C19 Power CordsC14 to C5 Power CordsC14 to NEMA 5-15 Power CordsC20 to C13 Power CordsC20 to C15 Power CordsC20 to C19 Power CordsC20 to C21 Power CordsInternational Power CordsMulti-Outlet Extension CordsNEMA Power CordsNEMA 1-15 Power CordsNEMA 5-15 to IEC 320 C13 Power CordsNEMA 5-15 to IEC 320 C15 Power CordsNEMA 5-15 to IEC 320 C19 Power CordsNEMA 5-15 to IEC 320 C5 Power CordsNEMA 5-15P to NEMA 5-15R Power Cords ExtensionNEMA 5-20 Power CordsNEMA 6-15 Power CordsNEMA 6-20 Power CordsNEMA L5-15 Locking Power CordsNEMA L5-20 Locking Power CordsNEMA L6-15P to C13 Power CordNEMA L6-20 Locking Power CordsNotebook Power CordsPRIME WIRE CablesPower Cord SplitterPower Plug AdaptersRight Angle Power CordsSecure SleeveWork LightsPower Strips (57)PDUPower Outlet Wall TapPower StripTimer / SwitchPower Supplies / Batteries (77)AC/DC AdaptersAlkaline BatteriesBatteries / B1 TerminalBatteries / B7 TerminalBatteries / T1 TerminalBatteries / T2 TerminalCar ChargerCell BatteryPower Distribution BoxesRegulated Power SupplyScooter Battery ChargersStep up/down transformerUPSUSB / Mobile ChargersSecurity Camera (354)Access control Reader / Cards & TagsAccessoriesActive Video balunsBox CameraBullet CameraCamera Cables/AdaptersCamera LensCamera Mounts / Housing BracketsCoax TranceiverDVRDVR / NVR ServerHidden/Covert Security CamerasIP CameraIR CameraIndoor Dome CameraLine FiltersLock BoxesMagnet Contact SensorMini Mobil DVR SystemMini/Board CameraOutdoor Dome CameraPC BalunsPTZ CameraPassive BalunsPower Supply WireSecurity MonitorSirenTesterVideo ConvertersVideo DistributorsWeb CameraTelephone (76)Coiled Handset CordsInline CouplerModular Bulk CablesModular CordsModular PlugModular Surfacemount BoxModular Wall PlateT AdaptersTelephone HeadsetTools & Testers (64)66/110 Punch DownAnti Static DevicesCoaxial Crimping ToolCompression ConnectorCutter/StripperD-Sub Pin Insert/Extract ToolDigital MultimeterElectrical TestersHand Tool KitLaser Distance MeterLight Lux MeterModular Plug Crimp ToolNetwork TesterPC Cables TestersTool KitsUSB (299)Control DeviceFile TransferMemory Card ReadersNetworking AdaptersPrinter SwitchesSerial/Parallel AdaptersSound AdaptersUSB AdaptersUSB CablesMicro USB 2.0 CablesMicro USB OTG CablesMini USB 2.0 4-pin CablesMini USB 2.0 5-pin CablesUSB 2.0 A Male to A Male CablesUSB 2.0 A Male to B Male CablesUSB 2.0 A Male to Type C Cables USB 2.0 Extension CablesUSB 3.0 CablesUSB Type C Video CablesUSB Charging StationUSB ExtendersUSB HubsVideo AdaptersCustom Promotional Products (524)Card Style USB Flash DrivesJewelry SeriesLeather USB Flash DrivesMetal SeriesMini DrivesPVC / Rubber SeriesPackagingPen Style USB Flash DrivesPlastic SeriesPortable USB Battery ChargerSwivel SeriesWood / Bamboo SeriesQuick Order Custom Cables Help / Customer Support Order Tracking Change / Cancel Order Shipping Information Schools & Government Payment Terms Returns / Refunds Warranty / Claims Will Call Contact Us Hours 8AM to 5PM M-F (PST) Same-Day Shipping if ordered before 2pm PST 1-888-275-8755 Account
Company
Help
About Us
Contact Us
FAQ
Shipping Info
Return Policy
Return Form
Effective on February 7, 2011
This privacy statement describes how SF CABLE, INC collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.sfcable.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
We collect the following personal information from you
Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences
As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.
We use this information to
Fulfill your order
Send you an order confirmation
Respond to customer service requests
Administer your account
Send you a catalog
Send you a newsletter
Send you marketing communications
Display content based upon your interests
Choice/Opt-Out
You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at customerservice@sfcable.com.
Information Obtained from Third Parties
If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.
Information Sharing
At SFCABLE , we have a huge respect for your privacy. Third parties (such as AdRoll) may place cookies on your browser for targeted advertising purposes. Information collected may include IP addresses, cookie identifiers and website activity.  If you have any questions about the details of our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at customerservice@sfcable.com.
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
We may also disclose your personal information
as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
if SF CABLE, INC is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.
PayPal
If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.
We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site.
Web beacons
Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.
We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of SF CABLE, INC. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at customerservice@sfcable.com
We provide two means for you to make a purchase on our site. You can either use our order form or a third party payment option. If you use our shopping cart, the transmission of sensitive information collected on our order form is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If you choose to use a third party payment option to pay for your order, its privacy statement and security practices will apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.
Additional Policy Information
Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.
Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information
To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at customerservice@sfcable.com.
Notification of Privacy Statement Changes
We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Contact Information
You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:
SF Cable, Inc 28300 Industrial Blvd Ste F Hayward, CA 94545 Email: customerservice@sfcable.com Phone: 510-264-9988
Thank You!We'll send you great deals and more!Follow us!
Company Info
28300 Industrial Blvd Ste F Hayward, CA 94545-4439
Toll Free : 1-888-275-8755Local : 1-510-264-9988Fax : 1-510-264-9989
